（目覚ましの音）
（烈子(れつこ)）痛っ
Ouch!
うう…
マジ 頭 痛い 痛(いて)てて…
My head really hurts.
しばらく お酒控えよう
No more alcohol for me.
ん？
何 このハンカチ
Whose handkerchief is this?
（かぐ音）
私のじゃない
It's not mine.
昨日
何があったんだっけ？
What happened last night?
あれ？
Huh?
えっ？ えっ？ えっ？
何？ 今の
What... was that?
♪～
RAGE
～♪
（フェネ子(こ)）こないだ
どうやって帰ったか覚えてる？
Do you remember
how you got back home?
気付いたら 家で寝てた
I woke up in bed.
何にも覚えてない
I don't remember anything.
自腹王子に
介抱してもらったことも？
Not even the Prince taking care of you?
覚えてない
No...
Excuse me, Retsuko.
（坪根(つぼね)）ちょっと 烈子さん
Yes!
あっ はい
これ 営業部の島田(しまだ)さんに
届けてきてちょうだい
Please deliver this to Shimada
in the Sales department.
はい 分かりました
Understood.
それと れさすけ君て分かる？
Do you know Resasuke?
彼に “出すものは 早めに出せ”
って くぎ刺しといて
Tell him to make his submissions ASAP.
不在なら メモでいいから
If he's not there, leave him a note.
（ハイ田(だ)）おう 烈子
（烈子）あっ
Hey, Retsuko.
あっ ハイ田君 おはよう
Oh, Haida. Good morning.
（ハイ田）あれ？
お前 缶コーヒーなんて
飲むやつだったっけ？
Since when do you drink canned coffee?
あっ これ？ アハハ…
何となく飲んでみたくなっちゃって
Oh, this? I thought I'd give it a try.
（ハイ田）フーン
あっ ごめん
Excuse me! Miss Tsubone asked me to hurry,
so I'll see you later.
坪根さんに せかされてるから
行くね
（ハイ田）あっ ああ
I see...
SALES DEPARTMENT
（烈子）さすがに営業は
みんな 出払っちゃってるか
Everyone is away at meetings, of course...
あれ？
Huh?
いた！
He's here!
（烈子）おはようございます
（足音）
Good morning.
（れさすけ）どうも
Hello.
坪根さんから 言づてがありました
I have a message from Miss Tsubone.
領収書を早めに出すように
とのことです
Please ensure
you submit the receipts ASAP.
それから…
And...
週末は いろいろ
ご迷惑おかけしちゃったみたいで…
It seems I was a pain at the weekend.
親切にしていただき
ありがとうございました
Thank you for helping me out.
ほんとに みっともない
ところを―
I must have been a sorry sight.
お見せしちゃって…
はっ
（烈子）あれ？
Whoa. Whoa!
あれ？
（結婚式の音楽）
Whoa! Whoa!
あれ？
（結婚式の音楽）
あれ～っ？
Whoa!
（トン）腰掛け！
Short-timer! Get this done.
これ 処理しとけ
わああっ
ありがとうございます！
Thank you. I'll do my best.
精いっぱい頑張ります！
（トン）お… おう
Oh... right...
腰掛け！
Short-timer! Tea!
茶！
（烈子）は～い
Coming!
（烈子）
世界が いつもと違って見える
The whole world looks different.
転職とか結婚退職とか―
Changing jobs,
getting married and quitting...
別に そんなこと
どうでもいいことだったんだ
That was never important!
恋に生きれば よかったんだ
All I needed was love!
KARAOKE
（鷲美(わしみ)･ゴリ）
好きな人ができた！？
You've fallen for someone?
エヘヘ…
（ゴリ）ん？
これは…
She has completely fallen for him.
だいぶ仕上がってるわね
こないだまで “好きな人なんて
いない”って言ってたのに
The other day, she told us
there was no one she liked.
（鷲美）実戦経験がないだけで―
She's inexperienced,
実は結構 ほれっぽいタイプ
だったのかもしれないわね
but it seems she's the type
that falls in love easily.
（ゴリ）どんな人？
（鷲美）写真ある？
-What is he like?
-Do you have a photo?
Sure, but it's kind of embarrassing...
ありますけど～
何か見せるの 恥ずかしいなあ
（ゴリ）見せなさいよ～
（烈子）え～ どうしようかな？
-Show us!
-Should I?
（ゴリ）見せなさいよ～
（烈子）どうしようかな？
-Show us!
-Should I?
（ゴリ）じゃ 見せなくていい
（烈子）この人なんですけど～
-OK, then. It's no big deal.
-Here he is.
（鷲美･ゴリ）ああー…
（ゴリ）
か… かっこいいんじゃない？
He seems cool... I guess.
ですよね かっこいいですよね？
I know, right? He's cool, isn't he?
（鷲美）
“あばたも えくぼ”って言うしね
They do say that love is blind.
（烈子）えっ？
（鷲美）何でもない
-What?
-Don't mind me.
他に どんなとこがよかったの？
What else do you like about him?
え～
（鷲美）教えてよ
Tell us!
え～ どうしようかな？
Oh, should I?
（鷲美）じゃ 教えなくていい
Fine. It's no big deal.
When I got drunk, he helped me recover.
私が酔っ払ったとき
すっごく優しくしてくれたんですよ
でも 優しいだけじゃなくて…
Not only is he kind...
何だか あの人の周りだけ
空気が違ってて…
but, somehow,
the air around him feels different.
いつも どこか
遠くを見てる感じで…
He's always staring into the distance.
理由は よく分からないけど―
I don't really know why...
一緒にいると
不思議と心が落ち着くんです
but when we're together, I feel calm.
よかったわね 烈子
I'm happy for you, Retsuko.
（鷲美）きっと すてきな人なのね
I'm sure he's wonderful.
アハハ… 恥ずかしいなあ
This is embarrassing.
あれ？ 何か思い出したら
泣けてきちゃった 変なの
I'm getting teary-eyed
just thinking about it. How strange!
I have to go to the bathroom!
ちょっと トイレ行ってきま～す
（ゴリ･鷲美）
かっこよくは ないわよね
He is not cool...
（鷲美）っていうか
この人 あれに似てない？
This guy reminds me of
a soft candy for babies.
ほら 赤ちゃんが食べる
軟らかいお菓子
分かる！ 私も同じこと思ってた
I know, right? My thoughts exactly!
SALES DEPARTMENT
（マヌ丸(まる)）何だよ
Well, Resasuke,
I never realized you were so smooth!
れさすけ お前
意外と やるじゃねえか
（れさすけ）えっ？ 何が？
I'm what?
それだよ
Look!
DID YOU FORGET YOUR INVOICE?
SUBMIT YOUR RECEIPTS SOON - RETSUKO
〝烈子〞って こないだ
合コンに来てた子だろ？
Isn't Retsuko the girl
who came to the mixer?
（れさすけ）うん とても
仕事熱心な人みたいだね
Yes, she seems to be very diligent.
（マヌ丸）はあ？
違(ちげ)えよ バカ 何言ってんだ
Think again, idiot.
What are you talking about?
どう見ても お前の気を引きたくて
わざわざ用事 作って 来てんだろ
She's obviously trying to nudge you
into asking her out.
文面が醸し出す雰囲気で分かれよ
You can literally smell it in these notes.
今度 デート誘ってやれ
Ask her out on a date.
（れさすけ）誰を？
（マヌ丸）烈子ちゃんをだよ！
-Who?
-Retsuko!
（れさすけ）何で？
（マヌ丸）“何で？”じゃねえ
-Why?
俺が本当に お前を―
Did you really think I invited you
to the mixer just to even out the numbers?
お飾りで 合コンに
連れ出したと思ってんのか？
I did it because I'm worried about you!
俺は これでも
お前を超心配してやってんだぞ
（れさすけ）何で？
（マヌ丸）うああ…
-Why?
-You don't have a girlfriend!
お前に彼女いねえからだよ！
（れさすけ）でも…
（マヌ丸）“でも”じゃねえ！
-But...
-Don't "but" me!
いいか？ 今から お前に
彼女を作るべき理由を―
Listen, I'll explain
why you need a girlfriend
論理的に分かりやすく―
段階を踏んで説明してやる
まず１つ…
in a simple and logical manner.
Reason one...
（目覚ましの音）
（烈子）今日も会えた
Today, we meet again.
わあ…
えっ？
デートします？
Would you like to go on a date?
はい
Yes...
ああ…
TEA ROOM
（携帯電話の操作音）
LET'S GO ON SUNDAY.
（烈子）ウフッ
WHERE AND WHEN SHOULD WE MEET?
（携帯電話の操作音）
（れさすけ）10時に現地集合
10 a.m., at our destination...
何で現地集合なんだよ！
Don't meet up at the destination!
最寄り駅から
一緒に行きゃあいいだろうが！
Meet her at the nearest station
and go together!
（れさすけ）何で？
（マヌ丸）“何で？”じゃねえ！
-Why?
-Don't "why" me!
LET'S MEET AT THE STATION.
（烈子）ウフッ
I JUST ARRIVED.
ARE YOU HERE?
RESASUKE?
I'M HERE.
（烈子）ウフン
（電車の走行音）
（烈子）今 私たち カップルです
Now, we're a couple.
どっから どう見ても…
No matter how you look at it,
we're a couple.
カップルです
休日をお楽しみの皆さん
大変お騒がせしております
To everyone enjoying their day off,
excuse my excitement.
今 私たちカップルが―
We, as a couple,
テーマパークに入場いたしま～す
are about to visit an amusement park!
♪～
（烈子の歌声）
Once upon a time
I was always crying inside my heart
（れさすけの歌声）
Once upon a time
I was always daydreaming
You're the Out-of-Pocket Prince
You're the Metal Princess
（烈子と
れさすけの歌声）
The two of us met at a mixer
A drunken office mixer
We work in different departments
But our hearts beat as one
～♪
（マヌ丸）どうしてる？
ちゃんとエスコートできてるか？
-Did you escort her?
-Yes, I did.
うん できてるよ
（マヌ丸）沈みゆく夕日を
浴びながら 手をつないだか？
-Did you hold hands at sunset?
-Yes, we did.
うん つないだよ
（マヌ丸）よーし 上出来だ
Great! Well done.
初デートってのは
男が最初に値踏みされる場だからな
Men are judged on the first date.
彼女に男らしいとこ 見せてやれよ
Show her that you're a real man!
痛っ 痛たた… ああ…
Ouch!
（れさすけ）ただいま
-I'm back.
-Hello again!
あっ おかえりなさい
あの…
ずっと歩いてて疲れません？
I expect all this walking around
has tired you out.
どこか お店でも入って
休みませんか？
Shall we find a restaurant
and take a break?
大丈夫
I'm fine.
（烈子）ん…
（れさすけ）僕 全然疲れてないよ
I'm not tired at all. Let's go.
行こう
はーい
Right...
ああ…
（花火の音）
（風の音）
（烈子）うう…
あの…
寒くないですか？
Aren't you cold?
大丈夫
I'm fine. I'm not cold at all.
僕 全然寒くないよ
（烈子）んん…
（烈子）は…
は…
KARAOKE
（くしゃみ）
エヘヘ…
もう すっごく楽しかったです！
We had... so much fun!
（ゴリ）よかったじゃない！
（鷲美）ムカついたりしなかった？
-That's great.
-Was there anything you got upset about?
カップルで ああいう場所 行くと
けんかするって言うじゃない
Couples usually fight
when they go to amusement parks.
そんなこと 全然なかったですよ
Not at all.
私を楽しませようと
積極的にリードしてくれて―
He took the lead
and made sure that I was enjoying myself.
意外と頼れる人だなあって
He is surprisingly dependable.
痛っ 痛たたた…
Ouch!
（鷲美）
ちょっと どうしたのよ？ その足
Wait, what happened to your foot?
（ゴリ）
だいぶ引っ張り回されたのね
Maybe he dragged her everywhere.
（鷲美）
デートの相手って 男子中学生？
Is he a schoolboy or something?
違いますよ～
Oh, please!
（鷲美）だとしたら
随分 気遣いのない男ね
As it turns out, he's not very attentive.
私だったら 途中で帰るわよ
-If I were you, I would have gone home.
-No way...
そんな…
新しい靴なんか履いていった
私が悪かったんです
It was my fault
for choosing brand new shoes.
SEND
（デスメタルの音楽）
（鷲美）いつものやつ 歌ったら？
Do you want to sing your usual song?
You must have a lot of pent-up anger.
何だかんだで
ストレスたまったでしょ？
そうよ！ 歌って
スッキリしちゃいなさい
Yes, release it by singing.
（烈子）
不満なんて 全然ないですから
I have nothing to complain about.
PAUSE
私 今 とっても幸せです
I'm really happy right now!
（烈子）
♪あなたは 自腹の
You're the Out-of-Pocket Prince
♪プリンス
（れさすけ）
♪君は メタルの
You're the Metal Princess
♪プリンセス
（烈子･れさすけ）
♪二人の出会いは
The two of us met at a mixer
♪合コン
♪飲みすぎた
A drunken office mixer
♪社内合コン
～♪
Subtitle translation: John Haguewood